muse-themes.com 2018-12-02

# MuseThemes - Privacy Policy

### **Your privacy is very important to us. Read below how we collect, store, use, and share your personal information.**

The following is an agreement between you as licensee and user (“You) and the owners of [MuseThemes.com](http://www.musethemes.com/) ("Website"), and Visual Arms Creative Corp. ("Owner,” “VA,” "We"). We at MuseThemes.com respect your privacy, are committed to protecting it and want you to be informed about the ways we protect, use and share the information that we collect.

This Privacy Policy (“Policy”) serves to inform you of our policies and procedures regarding the collection, use and disclosure of the information we receive when you visit www.musethemes.com or any other site built, hosted or operated via our Service or a part thereof (together, our “Site”), and when you use any part of our products or services available through the Site or other related websites, toolbars, conversion technology, widgets, applications or distribution channels we may operate from (the “Service”). This Policy applies to information that you provide to us through the Site or the Service, when you access or use any content appearing on the Site or made available through the Service, or that we collect on your behalf as part of the Service.

This Policy is an integral part of our Terms of Service (the “Terms of Service”).

If you have any questions about this Policy or do not agree with it, please contact our Data Protection Officer (“DPO”) using the details provided below before using the website: contact@musethemes.com.

## **Grounds For Information Collection**

Visual Arms Creative Corp. requests that customers supply personal data, which includes individually identifiable information, when placing orders, such as name, physical address, email address, and credit card information (“Personal Information”). This Personal Information is necessary for fulfilling orders, providing products and Services, communicating with customers, partners, or suppliers regarding orders, protecting our legitimate interest and complying with legal and financial regulatory obligations to which we are subject. We do not rent, sell, or share Users’ information with third parties except as described in this Privacy Policy.

When you use the Site, you consent to the collection, storage, use, disclosure and other uses of your Personal Information as described in this Privacy Policy.

We encourage our Users to carefully read the Privacy Policy and use it to make informed decisions. 

## Information We Collect

Visual Arms Creative Corp. collects Personal Information, including:

  * Your name and contact information, including your mobile phone number, email address and company details (including physical address, and phone number) which you may submit to us when you interact with the Website;
  * Information about location or similar location based information;
  * Billing information, including credit card number and billing address

In addition, when you use the Site, we automatically receive and record information from your browser or mobile platform, including your location, IP address, cookie information, and activity on the Site. This information is stored in our server logs in order to enhance the functionality of our Site.

## **What We Do With Collected Information**

We may use this information for the following:

  * Fulfilling purchases and providing our products and Services;
  * Communication regarding your purchases, our Services, and any activities surrounding the Company;
  * Updating records for the purpose of retaining records about you;
  * Protecting our legitimate interest;
  * Compliance with legal and financial regulatory obligations to which we are subject;
  * Improvement of the Company and Site;
  * Prevention of unlawful activities;
  * Evaluation of our marketing and for the purposes of research, training, and analysis of the Company

We may contact you by e-mail for the purposes set out in this section. By submitting such information to us, you are deemed to have agreed to us contacting you by email. We will continue to contact you using this method until you advise us in writing that you no longer wish to be contacted.

## **How We Collect Information**

We receive your Personal Information from various sources:

  * When you voluntarily provide us your personal details in order to register on our Site;
  * When you use or access our Site in connection with your use of our Services;
  * From third party providers, Services and public registers (for example, traffic analytics vendors)

## **Sub-User Information Collected**

As you use our Site, you may import into our system Personal Information you have collected from your customers. We have no direct relationship with your customers or any person other than you, and for that reason, you are responsible for making sure you have the appropriate permission for us to collect and process information about those individuals. Consistent with the uses of Personal Information covered above, we may transfer Personal Information of you or your customers to companies that help us promote, provide, or support the Company. We may use and incorporate into features information you have provided, we have collected from you, or we have collected about customers.

If you are a customer and no longer want to be contacted by one of our users, please unsubscribe directly by contacting the User directly to update or delete your data. If you contact us, we may remove or update your information within a reasonable time and after providing notice to the User of your request.

We will retain Personal Information we process on behalf of our Users for as long as needed to provide our Services or to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, prevent abuse, and enforce our agreements.

## **Managing Your Information**

Visual Arms Creative Corp. employs procedural and technological measures designed to protect your personally identifiable information from loss, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction. Where reasonably practical, Visual Arms Creative Corp. uses SSL and other encryption, password protection, firewalls, internal restrictions and other security measures to help prevent unauthorized access to your personally identifiable information.

Although we take reasonable steps to safeguard information, we cannot be responsible for the acts of those who gain unauthorized access or abuse our Site, and we make no warranty, express, implied or otherwise, that we will prevent such access.

## **User Rights**

You may request to:

  * Receive confirmation as to whether or not Personal Information concerning you is being processed, and access your stored Personal Information, together with supplementary information;
  * Receive a copy of Personal Information you directly volunteer to us in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format;
  * Request rectification of your Personal Information that is in our control;
  * Request erasure of your Personal Information;
  * Object to the processing of Personal Information by us;
  * Request to restrict processing of your Personal Information by us

If you have any questions or comments, or if you want to update, delete, or change any Personal Information we hold, or you have a concern about the way in which we have handled any privacy matter, please contact our DPO by email (contact@musethemes.com).

## **Marketing**

We may use your Personal information for the purpose of providing you with promotional materials, concerning the Company, which we believe may interest you.

These marketing materials will include an opportunity to decline receiving further marketing offers from us. If you unsubscribe we will remove your email address from our marketing distribution list.

Please note that even if you have unsubscribed from receiving marketing emails from us, we may send you other types of important email communications. These may include announcements about the Company, or about your individual account.

## **Cookies**

We use cookies and other technologies on our Site. A “cookie” is a small piece of information that a website assigns to your device while you are viewing a website. Cookies are very helpful and can be used for various different purposes. These purposes include allowing you to navigate between pages efficiently, enable automatic activation of certain features, remembering your preferences and making the interaction between you and our Site quicker and easier. Cookies are also used to help ensure that the advertisements you see are relevant to you and your interests and to compile statistical data on your use of our Site.

You can disable cookies in your browser and delete all cookies currently stored on your computer. You can find out how to do this by modifying your browser’s preferences appropriately.

##    
Retention

We will retain your Personal Information for as long as necessary to provide our Services, and as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our policies. Retention periods will be determined taking into account the type of information that is collected and the purpose for which it is collected, bearing in mind the requirements applicable to the situation and the need to destroy outdated, unused information at the earliest reasonable time. Under applicable regulations, we will keep records containing customer Personal Information, account signup agreements, communications and anything else as required by applicable laws and regulations.

## Sharing Information

Visual Arms Creative Corp. may only share personal information with partners or suppliers in order for them to fulfill the Service you have ordered. These organizations will have access only to the information required to permit them to perform their obligations to us.

We will only disclose your personally identifiable information if we reasonably believe we are required to do so by law, regulation or other government authority or to protect against fraud. We may transfer your personally identifiable information to a successor entity upon a merger, consolidation or other corporate reorganization in which Visual Arms Creative Corp. participates. Such successor entity shall be bound by the terms and conditions of this privacy policy.

##    
Links to Third Party Sites

This Site may be linked to other web sites on the Internet which are not under the control of or maintained by Visual Arms Creative Corp. Such links do not constitute an endorsement by Visual Arms Creative Corp. of those other web sites, the content displayed therein, or the persons or entities associated therewith. You acknowledge that Visual Arms Creative Corp. is providing these links to you only as a convenience, and you agree that Visual Arms Creative Corp. is not responsible for the content of such sites. Your use of these other linked web sites is subject to the respective terms of use and privacy policies located on the linked sites. We will not be responsible for the protection of any personal data which you provide to third party sites.

##    
Online Privacy Policy Only

This privacy policy applies only to our online activities and is valid for visitors to our website and regarding information shared and/or collected there. This policy does not apply to any information collected offline or via channels other than this website

Consent

By using our website, you hereby consent to our privacy policy and agree to its terms.

This Privacy Policy was last updated on: May 24, 2018.
